Surely, they're called power naps for a reason?
当然，它们被称为能量小憩是有原因的，对吧？
Aren't naps the key to feeling alert, improving your memory and just generally having a great life?
小憩不就是保持警觉、提高记忆力、甚至拥有美好生活的关键吗？
Well, they can be, but things aren't quite that simple.
嗯，它们可以是，但事情并没有那么简单。
It is true that a short nap can help people be more alert, improve their memory and concentration, and reduce risks around tasks with heavy machinery.
确实，短暂的小憩可以帮助人们更加警觉，提高记忆力和注意力，并降低操作重型机械相关任务的风险。
Our circadian rhythms are responsible for the notorious lull that many of us feel in the early afternoon.
我们的生物钟节律是造成许多人在午后感到倦怠的原因。
This is the best time for a nap.
这是小憩的最佳时间。
Some companies have installed sleep pods for their employees, hoping to benefit from increased productivity and cognitive performance.
一些公司为员工安装了睡眠舱，希望从员工提高的生产力和认知表现中受益。
But it is also true that naps can cause problems.
但同样真实的是，小憩也可能带来问题。
Let's start by thinking about the length.
让我们先考虑一下时长。
A true power nap should be less than half an hour.
真正的能量小憩应该少于半小时。
Any longer, and it becomes hard to rouse yourself from.
再长一些，就很难从睡意中清醒过来。
Any benefits in terms of alertness are likely to disappear with the grogginess that results from a longer period of slumber.
任何警觉性方面的好处都可能随着长时间睡眠带来的昏沉而消失。
This isn't the only issue.
这还不是唯一的问题。
Naps have been linked to conditions such as diabetes, high blood pressure and cardiac problems.
小憩与糖尿病、高血压和心脏问题等疾病有关。
However, it's not clear whether these are direct results, or stem from the impact of napping on our sleep habits.
然而，尚不清楚这些是直接结果，还是源于小憩对我们睡眠习惯的影响。
If you take a nap after about two or three in the afternoon, it's likely to have a negative effect on your ability to get to sleep at night.
如果你在下午两三点之后小憩，很可能会对你晚上入睡的能力产生负面影响。
Breaking your sleep cycle can lead to bad sleeping habits, which themselves become ingrained.
打乱你的睡眠周期会导致根深蒂固的不良睡眠习惯。
Of course, in the same way that naps can lead to bad sleep, it's also true that bad sleep can lead to wanting to take more naps.
当然，小憩会导致睡眠质量低，反之亦然。
So, if you find yourself frequently needing to sleep during the day, experts suggest that you consider why that's the case.
因此，如果你发现自己白天经常需要睡觉，专家建议你考虑一下原因。
Are there any potential health issues that could be causing insomnia?
是否有任何潜在的健康问题可能导致失眠？
Or are work pressures stopping you from getting enough sleep?
或者是工作压力阻碍你获得足够的睡眠？